Are you satisfied with your work?
Today?
We are talking about job satisfaction or the things people need to be happy at work.
What do you think is most important to people?
You might be surprised that it is not money.
One thing that many people look for a job that helps other people.
In general, people want to help other people.
They want to make the world a better place.
Teachers are normally at the top of the list of happiest jobs.
Every day, teachers help people learn and grow.
Think about your favorite teacher.
Most likely he or she was happy at work.
Another thing people want from a job is to create things.
They want to use their minds.
They don't want to be in a boring job.
They don't want to sit at a desk every day and look at a computer.
Engineers are also usually at the top of the list of happiest jobs.
Engineers create new products.
It's very exciting when they finally see their new product.
When was the last time you made something?
Did it make you happy?
Also, people want their boss to thank them for the work they do.
When a boss thanks their workers for their good work, they feel more satisfied with their jobs.
And when people are satisfied in their jobs, they try hard.
Finally, people want to have happy coworkers.
Everybody wants to enjoy their day at work.
When coworkers work hard, like their job, and are friendly, there's a good work environment.
A job is a lot of fun when you work together with other happy people.
Of course, there are other things that people look for in a job.
Money matters and where you work is important.
But overall, being happy is most important to many people for.